<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="com.genuitec.myeclipse.base"
      label="%featureName"
      version="8.5.0.me201003250245-DwCQ96GMKjrK79yy7Pw0FOilnmdS"
      provider-name="%providerName">

   <description url="%featureUrl">
      %description
   </description>

   <copyright url="%copyrightUrl">
      %copyright
   </copyright>

   <license url="%licenseUrl">
      End User License Agreement - MyEclipse
MyEclipse is a comprehesive and affordable Integrated Development
Environment (IDE) based on the Eclipse platform focusing primarily
on improving developers&apos; productivity by simplifying development
lifecycle in the delivery of UML, Web, J2EE, XML, JSP , JSF,
Struts, Hibernate and database applications. Currently supported
platforms include Windows, Linux and Mac OSX. 
PLEASE READ THIS END-USER LICENSE AGREEMENT CAREFULLY BEFORE
USING THE SOFTWARE. REGARDLESS OF HOW YOU ACQUIRE THE SOFTWARE
(ELECTRONICALLY, PRE-LOADED, ON MEDIA OR OTHERWISE), DOWNLOADING,
INSTALLING OR USING THE SOFTWARE SHALL INDICATE YOUR ACCEPTANCE
OF THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS CONTAINED IN THIS END-USER LICENSE
AGREEMENT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF
THIS END-USER LICENSE AGREEMENT, YOU MAY NOT DOWNLOAD, INSTALL
OR USE THE SOFTWARE. 
1.0 Definitions. 1.1)&apos;Licensor&apos; means Genuitec L.L.C.; 1.2)&apos;Subscriber&apos;
means registered members of the MyEclipse community whose dues
have been paid in full; 1.3)&apos;Update&apos; shall refer to maintenance
releases specific to the Software, as they will be made by Licensor
under no obligation or commitment to do so; 1.4)&apos;Software&apos; shall
mean the release version of MyEclipse, including any Content,
as downloaded by Subscriber or as provided on distribution media
in physical or electronic form; 1.5)&apos;Term&apos; refers to the effective
duration of the license agreement and is effective for 12 months
following possession of this software; 1.6) ‘Agreement’ shall
mean this End User License Agreement; 1.7) ‘Content’ means all
software and information in executable, binary or text form included
in the distribution media, on-line or in electronic form, embedded
data, programming, HTML, files, images, graphics, icons, Documentation
and all other content or materials incorporated in or generated
under the terms of this Agreement; and 1.8) ‘Documentation’ refers
to published product specifications and accompanying documentation.
2.0 Software. The Software is protected by copyright under United
States, foreign laws and international treaties. Unauthorized
use of the Software may violate copyright, trademark and other
laws. Licensor grants Subscriber the non-exclusive, non-transferable
right and license to permit one End User the use of the Software
on computer workstations located at his/her normal places of
business, during the Term and subject to the terms and conditions
of the Agreement. If Licensor provides Updates to Subscriber
during the Term, the Updates will be provided at no additional
charge. The terms of the Agreement will apply to all Updates
provided to Subscriber. This grant is not a transfer of title,
and under this license Subscriber may not: a) use, republish,
upload, post or transmit in any way the Software except as expressly
authorized pursuant to the Agreement; b) copy, reproduce, modify
or create derivative works from the Software except as expressly
authorized pursuant to the Agreement; c) attempt to decompile,
disassemble or reverse engineer the Software; d) remove any copyright
or other proprietary notations from the Software; e) distribute,
transfer, sale, lease, sublicense, assign or otherwise make available,
directly or indirectly, the Software, in part or in whole, including
any search output or results, to any other person; f) except
as may be specifically provided in the Agreement, permit the
Software to be accessed through an electronic network beyond
Subscriber&apos;s normal places of business; or g) transfer the Software
to another person or &apos;mirror&apos; the Software on external servers.
3.0 Limitation of Liability. Licensor assumes no responsibility
for the selection of the Software to achieve any intended purpose,
for the proper use of Software or for verifying the results obtained
from use of the Software. Licensee recognizes that the Software
will interact with software provided by other suppliers, and
accepts that Licensor assumes no responsibility for such use,
interaction, performance issues, or failure to achieve any desired
results. We warrant that for a period of 90 days after delivery
of this copy of the Software: a) if the Software is provided
on physical media by Licensor, the physical media on which this
copy of the Software is provided to you will be free from defects
in materials and workmanship under normal use, and b) the Software
will perform in substantial accordance with the Documentation.
To the extent permitted by applicable law, the foregoing limited
warranty is in lieu of all other warranties or conditions, express
or implied, and we disclaim any and all implied warranties or
conditions, including any implied warranty of title, non-infringement,
merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose, regardless
of whether we know or had reason to know of your particular needs.
No employee, agent, dealer or distributor of ours is authorized
to modify this limited warranty, nor to make any additional warranties.
Some states do not allow the limitation or exclusion of liability
for incidental or consequential damages, so the above limitation
may not apply to you. Licensor entire liability and Subscriber’s
exclusive remedy for breach of the foregoing warranty shall be,
at our option, to either: a) return the price you paid, or b)
repair or replace the Software that does not meet the foregoing
warranty if it is returned to us with a copy of your receipt.
In no event will Licensor be liable to you for any damages, including
any lost profits, lost savings, or other incidental or consequential
damages arising from the use or the inability to use the Software
(even if Licensor or an authorized dealer or distributor has
been advised of the possibility of these damages), or for any
claim by any other party. 
4.0 Termination of Agreement. The Agreement takes effect upon
your use of the Software and remains effective until terminated.
The Agreement shall immediately and automatically terminate without
notice or any other act upon i) the expiry of the Term; ii) the
attempted illegal copying, distribution, transfer, assignment,
lease or sale of the Software, or rights thereto, without the
prior written consent of Licensor; or iii) notice in writing
given by one party to the other upon the violation by that party
of any provision of the Agreement. Upon termination of the Agreement,
Subscriber will forthwith cease use of the Software and destroy
all originals and copies of the Software or any portion thereof,
stored in any form, including electronic form on any of its computer
equipment. Upon Licensor&apos;s request, Subscriber will provide a
written certification that all the copies of the Softwaren, in
whole or in part in any form have been destroyed. Failure to
do so may result in additional fees and charges being levied
against Subscriber. Any and all use of the Software by Subscriber
following termination of the Agreement is prohibited and may
result in additional fees and charges being levied against Subscriber.
5.0 Confidentiality. The Software contains trade secrets and
proprietary know-how that belong to the Licensor and it is being
made available to you in strict confidence. Any use or disclosure
of the Software, or of its algorithms, protocols or interfaces,
other than in strict accordance with the Agreement may be actionable
as a violation of licensor trade secret rights. 
6.0 Indemnity. Subscriber will indemnify Licensor and hold it
harmless from and against any and all claims which a third party
may assert against Licensor by reason of or as a consequence
of Subscribers use of the Software. 
7.0 General Provisions. The Agreement constitutes the entire
agreement between the parties and supersedes all prior agreements
and understandings, oral and written, express or implied, by
and between any of the parties with respect to the subject matter
of the Agreement. No amendment or modification of the Agreement
shall be binding unless in writing and signed by a duly authorized
representative of both parties. The Agreement shall be governed
by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of
Texas and federal laws of the United States. Any actions at law
or in equity arising out of or in relation to the Agreement may
be filed only in the state or federal courts of Dallas, Texas,
U.S.A. and Subscriber hereby consents and submits to the personal
and exclusive jurisdiction of such courts. If any one or more
of the provisions contained in the Agreement should be invalid,
illegal or unenforceable in any respect in any jurisdiction,
the validity, legality and enforceability of such provision or
provisions shall not in any way be affected or impaired as a
result of such event in any other jurisdiction and the validity,
legality and enforceability of the remaining provisions contained
in the Agreement shall not in any way be affected or impaired
as a result of such event, unless in either case as a result
of such determination the Agreement would fail in its essential
purpose. 
8.0 Copyright and Trademark Notices. The Software is trademarked
and Copyright © 2004-2009 Genuitec, LLC. 2221 Justin Rd #119-340,
Flower Mound, Texas, 75056 USA. Any rights not expressly granted
herein are reserved to the Licensor. By selecting the &apos;Accept
License&apos; button, you agree that you have reviewed the Agreement
and that you will comply with all of its terms and conditions.
   </license>

   <url>
      <discovery label="MyEclipse 8.0 Edition Discovery Site" url="http://downloads.myeclipseide.com/downloads/products/eworkbench/8.0/updates/"/>
   </url>

   <includes
         id="org.eclipse.emf"
         version="2.5.0.v200906151043"/>

   <includes
         id="org.eclipse.emf.ecore.sdo"
         version="2.4.0.v200902171115"/>

   <includes
         id="org.eclipse.gef"
         version="3.5.2.v20100111-1352-777928194B66D5D476C33B2A"/>

   <includes
         id="org.eclipse.xsd"
         version="2.5.0.v200906151043"/>

   <includes
         id="org.eclipse.xsd.edit"
         version="2.5.0.v200906151043"/>

   <includes
         id="com.genuitec.myeclipse.webtools"
         version="8.5.0.me201003250245-7k7EFkIFDHXuTKc_dcSMwqhCZdz-"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.aspphp.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.aspphp.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.ast.deploy.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003232017"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.browser"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003190322"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003250242"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.core.common"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003250241"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.core.common.platform"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003101716"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.cross.easystruts.eclipse"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003101716"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.jniwrapper"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.dtd"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.easie.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003232017"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.easie.sun"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003190322"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.easie.tomcat"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003190322"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.easie.tomcat.myeclipse"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003121946"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.examples"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.export.wizard"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.fileview"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.integration"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.j2eedt.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003231033"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.javascript"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003180050"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.memory"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.modeling.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.modeling.core.layout"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.portlet"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003101716"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.templates"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.wdt.jsp.debug"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.web.imagepreviewer"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.webdesigner3"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003231033"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.eclipse.wizards"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.javascript.debug"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003180050"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.javascript.debug.mozilla"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"
         fragment="true"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.jboss.ide.eclipse.apache.xalan"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.jboss.ide.eclipse.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.jboss.ide.eclipse.xdoclet.assist"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.jboss.ide.eclipse.xdoclet.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.jboss.ide.eclipse.xdoclet.run"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.jboss.ide.eclipse.xdoclet.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.myeclipse.compatibility"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.myeclipse.doc"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003250241"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.myeclipse.perspective"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003232017"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.genuitec.org.eclipse.webbrowser"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="8.5.0.me201003180050"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.ibm.icu"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="4.0.1.v20090822"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="net.sourceforge.lpg.lpgjavaruntime"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.1.0.v200803061910"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.aopalliance"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.apache.commons.collections"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="3.2.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.apache.commons.io"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.3.2.v20080604-1500"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.apache.commons.jxpath"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.2.0.v20080604-1500"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.apache.derby.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="10.5.1.1_v20100129"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.aspectj.aspectjrt"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.6.0.v200808071200"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.aspectj.aspectjweaver"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.6.0.v200805211800"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.hibernate.xml"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.hibernate.xml.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.albireo.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.3.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.atf.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.2.2.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.atf.mozilla.ide.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.2.2.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.atf.mozilla.ide.debug"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.2.2.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.atf.mozilla.ide.debug.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.2.2.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.atf.mozilla.ide.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.2.2.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.atf.mozilla.ide.ui.extras"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.2.2.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.atf.templates"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.2.2.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.atf.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.2.2.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.dali.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.dali.db"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.dali.edit"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.dali.gen"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.dali.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.dali.utility"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.5.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.draw2d"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="3.5.2.v20091126-1908"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.jpt.db"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.2.102.v200911250220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.jpt.utility"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.4.0.v200905310000"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.zest.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.1.0.v20090504-1850"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.zest.layouts"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.1.0.v20090504-1850"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.common"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.common.gef"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.common.kb"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.common.model"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.common.model.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.common.text.ext"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.common.text.xml"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.jsf"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.jsf.text.ext"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.jsf.text.ext.facelets"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.jsf.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.jsf.vpe.ajax4jsf"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.1.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.jsf.vpe.facelets"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.1.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.jsf.vpe.richfaces"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.1.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.jst.jsp"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.jst.web"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.jst.web.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.vpe"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.1.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.vpe.ui.palette"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.1.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.vpe.xulrunner"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.1.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jdom"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.0.0.v200806100616"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.mozilla.javascript"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.6.2.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.mozilla.xpcom"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.9.0.7-me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.objectweb.asm"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.2.3"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.jpt.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.2.1.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.common.el.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.common.resref.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.0.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.common.resref.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.0.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.jsf.vpe.jsf"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.1.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.jsf.vpe.jstl"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.1.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.jsf.vpe.myfaces"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.1.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.vpe.html"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.1.0.me201003052220"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.jboss.tools.vpe.resref"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0.me201003052220"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
